http://ma-research.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy.
The following policies are in effect for the web pages, newsletters and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by Managed Account Research Incorporated (“MARI Network”), which includes MA-Research.com and CTA-Info.com.
Technical Information Collected
Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers known as the “Internet Protocol” IP address. Like most web servers, when a visitor requests a page from any Web Site within the MARI Network our servers automatically recognize and log that visitor’s domain name, IP address, access times, referring web sites, platform, and browser type. This information reveals nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use these logs to provide statistics about our Web site usage in aggregate, to assist us in the maintenance, design, and operation of our Web site, and to investigate misuse of the MARI Network, its users, or to cooperate with law enforcement. We do not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals. Our Web servers do not automatically record e-mail addresses of the visitors.
Information on Cookies
When using our sites, MARI or its advertisers may send a “cookie” to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of MARI’s Network of Web Sites you have visited, personalized or customized, so the next time you visit those pages may be readily accessible. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you’ve seen an advertisement. We and our advertisers may use this information to better personalize the content and promotions that you see on our Site. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our site and other Web sites will not work as intended.
Registration Data
MARI offers access to services that are free but that may require registration. We will use your registration contact information to send notification of MARI products and services by e-mail and/or postal mail. We also may share that information with our affiliates and clients. Our affiliates and clients may send you promotional material that is related to the topic of the service for which you registered unless you have chosen not to receive it. MARI reserves the right to send to our registered members email notices and announcements that may be of interest to MARI users. TO NOT RECEIVE ANY COMMUNICATION FROM MARI, MEMBERS SHOULD REQUEST THAT THEIR REGISTRATION BE CANCELLED. We respect and will honor all requests to correct, erase, or otherwise act in our visitor’s wishes in regards to the use of their data.
Email Announcements and Opting-out
We will most likely also request your e-mail address and other personal information for the purposes of providing additional services (for example, subscriptions to email newsletters or updates). Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested. You can unsubscribe from our newsletters or by following the instructions at the bottom of every email.
Through our Web site you may also subscribe to promotional announcements from our partners. Our site provides users the opportunity to choose or opt-out of receiving communications from MARI sites and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. For example, during our Free Report sign up for the Free Report on Trading we will ask if it is alright to send these promotional announcements. If you do not wish to receive the announcements you have the ability to opt-out.
Third-Party Offers
Some advertisers we work with are interested in acquiring leads for their sale force by providing offers that qualify visitors. For example, a brokerage might provide a free book on trading in order to reach and advertise to that audience. (This is known as cost-per-lead advertising (CPL) or co-registration.)
With third-party offers user data is collected by our webservers and sent to the advertiser who then fulfills the offer. After data is sent to the advertiser we have no way to control how it is used because it has left our system. We always attempt to deal with reputable companies who respect user privacy but we cannot guarantee, or be liable for, any misuse of visitor data as a result of a third-party offer on our site. If you have experienced a problem with one of our advertisers, please tell us.
Single-pixel Images
MARI and its advertisers may use single-pixel gif images, sometimes referred to as web bugs or web beacons, to count Web page accesses and gather some general statistical information. MARI does not gather personal information through the use of these images. Our advertisers may use single-pixel gifs that can track personal information from cookies that may have been previously placed on a user’s computer by an advertiser.
Disclosure Where Required by Law
MARI will disclose personal information and/or an IP address, when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:
Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities or comply with legal process served on MARI,
Protect and defend the rights or property of the MARI Network and related properties, or visitors to the MARI Network and related properties,
Identify persons who may be violating the law, website terms of use, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing the MARI Network or its related properties.
Security of Data
MARI uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. MARI reserves the right to transfer all such information in connection with the sale of all or part of MARI’s capital stock or assets. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. We are not responsible for such third party privacy policies or how they treat information about their users.
Third Party Links
The MARI Network of Web sites contains many hyperlinks to other Web sites and from Affiliate Web sites. The MARI Web Sites may also contain advertisements of third parties. MARI is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites or advertisers. MARI does not share any of the individual personal information you provide MARI with the websites to which MARI links, except as stated elsewhere within this Privacy Policy, although MARI may share aggregate data with such websites (such as how many people use our site).
Your Consent to This Agreement
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by MARI as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Please send any questions about MARI’s Privacy Policy to:
Managed Account Research Incorporated
144 W Jackson, Ste 1710-A
Chicago, IL 60604
ADDITIONAL INFORMATION
The following legal information has been furnished for your convenience. Managed Account Research Incorporated may modify any of the information, and such modifications shall take effect immediately upon their posting upon this Web site.
About Us
Managed Futures Basics
Services
Individual Investors
Institutional Allocators
CTAs and CPOs
MARI Library
Research
Thanks for sending your message! We'll get back to you shortly.
There was a problem while sending your message. Please try again.
Please complete all the fields in the form before submitting it.
Please insert a valid email address.
